corsis.com 2018-07-17

# Privacy Policy - Corsis LLC

**Last updated:   November 9, 2016**

 CORSIS LLC (the “Company”) is committed to protecting the privacy of you and your company. We provide this notice to explain the type of information we collect on the Corsis applications, website, and system (together, the “Program”), and how that information is used. By using the Program, you signify your consent to the Terms and Conditions and this Privacy Policy.  If you do not agree with any term in the Terms and Conditions or this Privacy Policy, please do not use this site or submit any personally identifiable information. This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through the Program and not to information collected offline. We may revise this privacy statement from time to time. We recommend that you regularly check this page to ensure that you have read the most recent version.

  **Use of Your Information**

 We collect information from you when you utilize the Program, including information about your Company’s technological proficiency and other processes. The Company uses the information we collect to provide the services requested. This information is also used to improve and personalize your experience on our Program, and to allow us to better respond to your Company’s needs. We may also use your information to process transactions. We use return email addresses to answer the email that we receive, and we may occasionally use such email addresses to send you other information. We may use information for internal marketing analysis, for example, to assess trends among our users or to measure the amount of traffic to our websites. We may also share non-personal information with others in aggregate anonymous form, which means that the information will not contain any personally identifiable information about you or your company. For example, certain of your information may be used with the information of other similarly-situated entities as part of industry-wide analysis and comparisons.

 The Company may also use collected information for marketing purposes – for example, to arrange for selected organizations to send you marketing and promotional information that may be of interest to you. Information may also be shared with the Company’s business partners. In such circumstances your information may be disclosed to these organizations who will agree to be bound by the terms of this privacy statement and in a format that will not enable identification of your company. We will obtain your permission before we make any such disclosure.

 We may disclose your information if permitted by law or required to do so by law or where we believe such action is necessary in order to protect or defend our interests or the interests of users of the website. In the event of a sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization or liquidation, we may transfer, sell, or assign to third parties information concerning your relationship with us, including without limitation, information that you provide and other information concerning your relationship with us. We may transfer your information to third parties under confidentiality obligations when the performance of any service in relation to the activities above is sub-contracted.

  **Website Navigation Information**

 The Company uses commonly-available tools (such as cookies and web beacons) to collect information as you navigate this website and utilize the Program. Cookies are files or pieces of information that may be stored in your computer's hard drive when you visit a web site. Cookies may also be used to help speed up your future activities or to improve your user experience by remembering the information that you have already provided to us. We do not use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not voluntarily provided by you. The use of cookies is an industry standard. Web beacons are graphic images used to monitor users’ interactions with websites and/or emails. For example, the Company may use web beacons in emails sent to you to in order to ascertain how you interact with the Company’s emails.

  **Security**

 We take reasonable precautions to keep your personal information secure.  We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

 No transmission of data over the internet is guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under the control of the Company to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. While we strive to protect your information, neither the Company nor any of our service providers can ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us over the Internet. Any such transmission is done at your own risk.

  **Sharing Information With Third Parties**

 Unless otherwise identified in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your identifiable information without your prior authorization. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating the Program, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

  **Other Sites & Links**

 The Program may contain links or references to other websites outside of our control. Please be aware that we have no control over these sites and our privacy statement does not apply to these sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements and terms and conditions of linked or referenced sites you enter.

  **Information Collected by the Company and Correction Requests**

 You may request we provide you the information we hold about you, update your information or ask us to remove your information or correct any inaccuracies in such personal data. We will use reasonable efforts to respond to your request within a reasonable time. Please address your request to privacy@corsis.com. We will send our response only to the email address or mail address that we have on file for the visitor name that is associated in our database for such information.

 If at any time you wish to change, correct, or update your personal information, or if you have any questions or concerns about the Terms and Conditions or this Privacy Policy, please send your request to privacy@corsis.com. Please be sure to include your email address, full name, and postal address.

  **Applicable Law**

 The laws and regulations in different countries impose different (and even conflicting) requirements on the Internet and data protection. We are located in the USA, as are the servers which make this site available worldwide. All matters relating to this site are governed by the laws of the State of New York in the USA. Please note that any information you provide will be transferred to the USA and by submitting the information you authorize this transfer.

  **Changes to this Privacy Statement**

 The Company reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy, and will provide notification of material changes to this Privacy Policy at least thirty (30) business days prior to the change taking effect.
